Guide to the Minister to the University (Dean of the Chapel) records, 1940-1984 UA.17.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Reports for 1960-1961 Report Volume DURC (Box 7)
- 1961-1962 Reports/1962-1963 Organization for Publication (Box 7)
- Annual Report - Already Typed on Stencils, 1962-1963 (Box 7)
- 1964 Annual Reports DURC (Box 7)
- University Religious Council, 1956-1959 (Box 7)
- Miscellaneous DURC/Social Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 7)
- Constitutional Revisions, 1957-1958 (Box 7)
- DURC Executive Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 7)
- University Religious Council Minutes, 1957-1959 (Box 7)
- Layout of 1957-58 Annual Report, 1957-1958 (Box 8)
- U.R.C. - Executive Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 8)
- U.R.C. Personnel, 1959-1960 (Box 8)
- U.R.C. Executive Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 8)
- D.U.R.C. Membership, 1960-1962 (Box 8)
- D.U.R.C., 1960-1963 (Box 8)
- D.U.R.C. Matters, 1961-1962 (Box 8)
- Agenda and Minutes, DURC Executive Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 8)
- DURC Annual Report, 1961-1962 (Box 8)
- Prospective Members of DURC, 1960-1963 (Box 8)
- Fall Retreat, URC, 1957-1962 (Box 8)
- Meetings of the Full Council DURC, 1963-1964 (Box 8)
- DURC Executive Committee Minutes, 1963-1966 (Box 8)
- Musical Writing Contest, 1959 (Box 8)
- Potential Student Workers, Officers, undated (Box 8)
- Annual Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
- Ethical Decisions in Political Life, 1976 (Box 8)
- Wilmington 10, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
- Technological Apocalypse and A Theology of Hope, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
- Social Issues -- Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 8)
- YMCA - Affirmative Action Guide, 1979 (Box 8)
- DURC Executive Committee Minutes, 1968 (Box 8)
- Chapel Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
- IBM Statements Agency Budgets, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
- Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
- Religious Activities, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
- Mary - Budget Workpapers, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
- Bob - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
- Summer School Budget, 1974-1976 (Box 8)
- Information - Budget, undated (Box 8)
- Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
- Project Bolivia, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
- Project Nicaragua, 1963-1970 (Box 8)
- El Salvador, 1966-1971 (Box 8)
- Project Chile, 1971 (Box 8)
- Project Latin America, 1969 (Box 8)
- Akbar Abdul Haqq, 1964-1965 (Box 8)
- Faculty Forum, 1959-1971 (Box 8)
- Re-examination of Faith, 1964 (Box 8)
- Faculty Program Committee, 1957-1968 (Box 8)
- Faculty, 1970 (Box 8)
- Fellowship of Christian Athletes, 1968 (Box 8)
- FCA, 1959-1971 (Box 8)
- Duke Univ. Religious Council Faculty Program Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 8)
- FCA Article for Motive, 1964-1965 (Box 8)
- FCA Charlotte and Winston-Salem trip of James Jeffrey and H.C.W., 1964 (Box 8)
- FCA National Advisory Council, 1965 (Box 8)
- Dr. F.L. "Buzzy" Harrison, Jr., 1963-1970 (Box 8)
- Duke FCA. Budget, 1966-1969 (Box 8)
- Lake Geneva, Wisconsin, 1966 (Box 8)
- FCA Kansas City Planning Meeting, 1966 (Box 8)
- Homer C. Rice, undated (Box 8)
- Dr. Danny Lotz/Anne Graham Lotz, Billy Graham's daughter, 1969 (Box 8)
- FCA - Platform Addresses National Summer Conference, 1963-1964 (Box 8)
- Fellowship of Christian Athletes, 1963-1967 (Box 8)
- FCA, 1959-1964 (Box 9)
- DUCC, 1969-1973 (Box 9)
- DUCC - Special Observances Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 9)
- Duke U.C.M., 1965-1971 (Box 9)
- Task Group, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
- Freshman Orientation, 1957-1967 (Box 9)
- Wind and Chaff, 1966-1967 (Box 9)
- 2nd Look UCM, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
- Minutes - VII General Assembly, 1966 (Box 9)
- Chapel Staff, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
- Sanctuary, 1976 (Box 9)
- Reggie Howard Memorial Service, 1976 (Box 9)
- Speed Reading Course Recognition Ben Smith, 1978 (Box 9)
- Student Preacher Outlines, 1978 (Box 9)
- Bernstein Mass, 1978 (Box 9)
- Board of Managers and Pastors School, 1977 (Box 9)
- Board of Ordained Ministry, 1977-1978 (Box 9)
- Campus Ministries Conference, 1975 (Box 9)
- Commencement Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
- Convocation, 1976 (Box 9)
- Bishop Earl G. Hunt, Jr., 1976 (Box 9)
- Lyons, Harriet, 1977 (Box 9)
- Religious Life Staff, 1972-1977 (Box 9)
- DUPM Advisory Council, 1976-1977 (Box 9)
- Gooden, Al, 1977 (Box 9)
- DUPM Advisory Council, 1977-1978 (Box 9)
- DUPM Staff, 1977-1978 (Box 9)
- Fran Phillips, undated (Box 9)
- Reis, Paul, 1977 (Box 9)
- Jansen, Robert, 1975 (Box 9)
- Kernodle, John, 1974-1976 (Box 9)
- Davis, Gregg, 1977 (Box 9)
- Religious Life Staff, 1977-1978 (Box 9)
- Elkins, Heather, 1978 (Box 9)
- Pam McDaniel, 1978 (Box 9)
- Allen, Wayne, 1978 (Box 9)
- Friends, 1978 (Box 9)
- Baccalaureate Sermons, 1973 (Box 9)
- Dr. Hugh Anderson, 1973 (Box 9)
- Womble, B.S., Remarks, Founders Day 1960 (Box 9)
- Identifying the Roots of Oppression in the Church Barbara R. Thompson, 1977 (Box 9)
- Spiritual Survival for Women in the Ministry Donna Schaper, undated (Box 9)
- Edgemont Community Center I, 1941-1957 (Box 9)
- Edgemont Community Center II, 1947-1955 (Box 9)
- Edgemont Community Center III, inc. 3 Photos, 1953-1960 (Box 9)
- Edgemont Community Center Reports of Director, 1954-1956 (Box 9)
- Edgemont Community Center Reports of Director, 1957-1961 (Box 9)
- Edgemont Community Center Reports of Treasurer, 1942-1955 (Box 9)
- Edgemont Community Center Reports of Treasurer, 1956-1961 (Box 9)
- Edgemont Community Center Publicity, 1945-1957 (Box 9)
- Edgemont Community Center Minutes, 1958-1961 (Box 9)
- Duke University Church, 1937-1956 (Box 9)
- Univ. Religious Council, 1956-1961 (Box 10)
- Anniversary Chapel Concert, 1975 (Box 10)
- Summer Worship, 1975 (Box 10)
- Commencement, 1975 (Box 10)
- Flentrop Organ Dedication, 1976 (Box 10)
- Biographical Information on Past Chapel Preachers Words of Suggestion, 1964-1972 (Box 10)
- Duke University Services of Holy Communion, undated (Box 10)
- Religious Affiliation Tabulation, 1949-1956 (Box 10)
- Printing, 1965 (Box 10)
- Finance, 1961-1966 (Box 10)
- Summer School Budget, 1958-1972 (Box 10)
- DURC Budget, 1961-62 (Box 10)
- DURC, 1956-1972 (Box 10)
- DUCC Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
- Racism at Duke, 1972 (Box 10)
- Social Services Comm. YWCA, 1960-1965 (Box 10)
- Cabinet Business YWCA, 1966-1967 (Box 10)
- The University Experience, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
- Fellowship Leader - Bassett, 1962-1963 (Box 10)
- Annual Report 1972-1973, YM/YWCA (Box 10)
- YMCA Annual Report, 1966-1971 (Box 10)
- YWCA National Board I and II, 1971 (Box 10)
- Theologian in Residence, 1977-1980 (Box 10)
- Theologian in Residence, Holocaust Notes, 1977-1978 (Box 10)
- Continuing Education for Campus Ministry I and II, 1973-1977 (Box 10)
- Sound System, 1974 (Box 10)
- Bicentennial Celebration, 1976 (Box 10)
- Worship Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
- D.U. Parish Ministry, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
- D.U.P.M. Advisory Council, 1974-1976 (Box 10)
- Samuel V. Duh, 1975 (Box 10)
- 1975 Divinity Class Reunion (Box 10)
- Rotary Club, 1974 (Box 10)
- Kiwanis Club, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
- Jack Jackson, 1976 (Box 10)
- Larry Herndon, 1975 (Box 10)
- Harvey Estes, 1975 (Box 10)
- Student Address, 1973 (Box 10)
- Frances Redding, 1975 (Box 10)
- Duke Christian Unity, Sub of DUCC, undated (Box 10)
- H. H. Crane, 1944-1946 (Box 11)
- Chapel Bookkeeper, 1964-1970 (Box 11)
- Budgets, 1954-1972 (Box 11)
- Religious Activities Staff, 1952-1953 (Box 11)
- Chapel Ushers and Collectors, 1960-1970 (Box 11)
- Abortion, 1978 (Box 11)
- Accident or Death, 1973 (Box 11)
- Africa, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
- Advising Information Directory, AID, 1971-1974 (Box 11)
- Altar Pieces Committee, undated (Box 11)
- Alternative Vocations, 1975-1976 (Box 11)
- Amnesty -- Vietnam, 1974 (Box 11)
- Appalachian Project, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
- Arts in Duke Chapel, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
- Baptism Certificate [blank example], undated (Box 11)
- Baptist Student Union, 1980 (Box 11)
- Battered Women, 1979 (Box 11)
- Big Sister/Big Brother Program, 1978 (Box 11)
- Bill Griffith Staff, 1974-1976 (Box 11)
- Black Campus Minister, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
- Black Campus Ministry, 1975-1978 (Box 11)
- Black Minister, 1980 (Box 11)
- Black/White Students, undated (Box 11)
- Board of Ministry General Conference, 1974-1980 (Box 11)
- Campus Ministry -- Continuing Education, 1975-1978 (Box 11)
- Campus Ministry Articles, 1970's (Box 11)
- Campus Ministry, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
- Campus Minister's Continuing Education Mailing List, 1976 (Box 11)
- Campus Ministry Women, 1976-1979 (Box 11)
- Career Options Day, 1978 (Box 11)
- Chapel, 1978 (Box 11)
- Chapel Attendant Notes, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
- Chapel Attendants, 1975-1980 (Box 11)
- Chapel Brochure, 1975 (Box 11)
- Chapel Players, 1974 (Box 11)
- Chapel Preachers, 1976-1980 (Box 11)
- Duke Chapel Preaching Schedule Forms, 1980 (Box 11)
- Chapel Staff, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
- Chapel Worship, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
- Christmas Party, 1979 (Box 11)
- Clergy Couples, 1980 (Box 11)
- Committee to the Reverse the Arms Race, undated (Box 11)
- Conferences, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
- Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
- Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 12)
- Day Care, 1974 (Box 12)
- Death Penalty, 1975 (Box 12)
- Disarmament, 1980 (Box 12)
- Divinity School Intern, 1977-1979 (Box 12)
- Divorced-Separated-Formerly Married, 1977 (Box 12)
- Donuts, 1974 (Box 12)
- The Draft, 1980 (Box 12)
- Drama, 1976 (Box 12)
- DUCC, 1972-1974 (Box 12)
- Duke Chapel as Church, 1976-1981 (Box 12)
- Duke Student Foreign Mission Endowment Fund, 1978-1979 (Box 12)
- Duke Gardens Worship Service, 1970's (Box 12)
- DUPM Advisory Council, 1971-1979 (Box 12)
- DUPM Development, 1974 (Box 12)
- DUPM -- Fall Retreat Letters, 1976 (Box 12)
- DUPM -- Goals and Objectives, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
- DUPM -- Finance Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 12)
- DUPM -- Finance, 1977-1978 (Box 12)
- DUPM -- Firesides, undated (Box 12)
- DUPM -- General Papers, 1974 (Box 12)
- DUPM -- Pastoral Care/Nurture/Community, 1975-1976 (Box 12)
- DUPM -- Prophetic Concerns, 1978 (Box 12)
- DUPM Staff, 1978-1980 (Box 12)
- Duke University Faculty Women's Network, 1978 (Box 12)
- Duke Y, 1977-1978 (Box 12)
- Communications about DUPM, 1975-1976 (Box 12)
- DUPM, 1974-1980 (Box 12)
- DUPM Advisory Council, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
- DUPM Staff Group, 1977-1978 (Box 12)
- DUPM Staff, 1974-1977 (Box 13)
- DUPM Task Forces, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
- Durham Boys Choir, 1980 (Box 13)
- Durham District -- UMC, 1978 (Box 13)
- East Campus Facilities, 1974 (Box 13)
- East Campus Student Center, 1974 (Box 13)
- Edgemont, 1974 (Box 13)
- Edgemont Community Center Bulletin Inserts, undated (Box 13)
- Elected Officials, 1976 (Box 13)
- Energy, 1979 (Box 13)
- Episcopal University Center, 1980 (Box 13)
- Equal Rights Amendment Pamphlets, undated (Box 13)
- Evaluation Staff, 1976 (Box 13)
- Faculty Associates Meeting, 1980 (Box 13)
- Expressway Alternatives, 1978 (Box 13)
- Faculty Associates, 1974-1979 (Box 13)
- Faith and Arts, 1980 (Box 13)
- Field Education Evaluation Report, 1977-1980 (Box 13)
- Filing, 1974 (Box 13)
- Founder's Day, 1974 (Box 13)
- Friends of the Chapel, 1977-1981 (Box 13)
- General, 1972-1977 (Box 13)
- General Conference, 1980 (Box 13)
- General -- Social Concerns, 1977 (Box 13)
- Grad Students, 1978 (Box 13)
- Grant -- Board of Global Ministries the United Methodist Church Women, 1976-1977 (Box 13)
- Greensboro, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
- Guess Road Correctional Facility, 1974 (Box 13)
- Guidelines for Lector, 1978-1979 (Box 13)
- Honor Codes, undated (Box 13)
- Lena Horne Gala, 1980 (Box 13)
- Human Liberation Group, undated (Box 13)
- Human Sexuality, 1976-1979 (Box 13)
- Hunger, 1975-1980 (Box 13)
- Hunger Committee -- University, 1978-1979 (Box 13)
- Ideas from Other Places, 1973-1979 (Box 13)
- Interest Sheets, 1975 (Box 13)
- International Women's Year, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
- International Year of the Child, 1979 (Box 13)
- Internship, undated (Box 13)
- Interpreter's House, 1972 (Box 13)
- Interviews, 1979 RESTRICTED (Box 13)
- Jane Clark Moorman, 1978-1979 (Box 13)
- Jewish Campus Minister, 1978 (Box 13)
- Jewish-Christian Conversation, 1978-1979 (Box 13)
- Justice, 1978 (Box 13)
- Lecture Series, 1973 (Box 13)
- Liberation Theology, undated (Box 13)
- Lutheran Campus Minister, 1978-1980 (Box 13)
- Martin Luther King, Jr. Service, 1975-1980 (Box 13)
- Meeting Space, 1980 (Box 13)
- Ministries to Blacks in Higher Education, 1978 (Box 13)
- Ministry in the National Parks, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
- Mission Education, 1979 (Box 14)
- Muirhead Funeral, 1976 (Box 14)
- Music Dedication, 1974 (Box 14)
- NACUC, 1978-1980 (Box 14)
- National Institute of Campus Ministries -- NICM, 1975-1978 (Box 14)
- NICM -- Council of Advisors, 1975-1978 (Box 14)
- NC Council of Churches, 1979 (Box 14)
- Nuclear Energy, 1978 (Box 14)
- Organ Students, undated (Box 14)
- Orientation, 1975 (Box 14)
- Parables, 1979 (Box 14)
- Peace Issues, 1980 (Box 14)
- Penal Reform, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
- People's Alliance, 1975-1977 (Box 14)
- Personnel, 1980 (Box 14)
- Phone Numbers, 1972-1974 (Box 14)
- P.I.S.C.E.S., 1976 (Box 14)
- Posters, undated (Box 14)
- Preaching Committee, 1980 (Box 14)
- Preaching Schedule, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
- Prophetic Concerns Committee, 1978 (Box 14)
- Previous Self Studies, 1972 (Box 14)
- Prison Symposium, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
- Program Resources, 1978-1980 (Box 14)
- Publications, 1980 (Box 14)
- Pulpit Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 14)
- Religious Life Staff, 1977-1979 (Box 14)
- Refugees, 1979 (Box 14)
- Reggie Howard Memorial Service, 1976 (Box 14)
- Regional Conference, 1977 (Box 14)
- Religion and the Arts, 1979 (Box 14)
- Religious Census, 1979 (Box 14)
- Potter, 1976 (Box 14)
- Reproduction Rights, 1979 (Box 14)
- Residence Halls, 1969 (Box 14)
- Retreat Locations, 1969 (Box 14)
- Southern Appalachian Ministry in Higher Education, SAM, 1978-1979 (Box 14)
- Schools of Christian Mission, 1979 (Box 14)
- Self-Study -- Campus Ministry, 1976 (Box 14)
- Self Study, 1975 (Box 14)
- Publications, 1974 (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 14)
- Commencement, 1976 (Box 14)
- Annual Conference, 1976 (Box 14)
- NC United Methodist Chaplains, 1974 (Box 14)
- Duke University Alumni Association, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
- Ecumenical Campus Ministry Conference, 1975 (Box 14)
- Chapel Preaching Schedule, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
- General Conference, 1976 (Box 14)
- Chapel Worship Committee, 1974 (Box 14)
- Baccalaureate Preacher Sub-Committee, 1973 (Box 14)
- Commencement Committee, 1974 (Box 14)
- DU 50th Anniversary Advisory Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
- Continuing Education for Campus Ministry, 1974 (Box 14)
- Chapel Renovations, 1972-1973 (Box 15)
- Office Renovations, 1975 (Box 15)
- Student Workers, undated (Box 15)
- Miss Lucy Austin, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
- Cathy Carleson, 1973 (Box 15)
- Wilbert Mickens, 1974 (Box 15)
- Virginia Moye, 1974-1975 RESTRICTED (Box 15)
- Joyce L. Painter Assistant Organist, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
- Fred Roberts, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
- Wiley, John, 1975 RESTRICTED (Box 15)
- Lynn Zeigler, 1975 (Box 15)
- Pete Wilson, 1973 (Box 15)
- Clarence G. Newsome, 1972 (Box 15)
- Gary Greene, 1975 (Box 15)
- Denominational Chaplain Interviews, 1972-1973 (Box 15)
- Jim Caldwell, 1975 (Box 15)
- Tidings Supply House, 1974 (Box 15)
- Environmental Center, 1973 (Box 15)
- Recruitment Trips, 1973 (Box 15)
- TRAP, 1974 (Box 15)
- The Black Professional in the University, 1974 (Box 15)
- Steve Sapp, 1974 (Box 15)
- Floyd Gulick, Jr., 1974-1975 (Box 15)
- Brown Foundation, 1973 (Box 15)
- DUCC Budget Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
- Chapel Organ Fund, 1974 (Box 15)
- Christian Council Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 15)
- Political Action in Christ, PAX, 1974 (Box 15)
- The Jewish Chautauqua Society, 1974 (Box 15)
- The University Letter, 1975 (Box 15)
- Associate and Assistant Ministers, 1973 (Box 15)
- October, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
- Cleland Honorary Service, 1974 (Box 15)
- Chapel Administrative Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 15)
- Contemporary Drama, Movies, TV and Religious Thought, 1974 (Box 15)
- Divinity School Information, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
- Chapel Staff Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
- Mary Cash, 1974 RESTRICTED (Box 15)
- Dedication -- The M.D.B. Music Building, 1974 (Box 15)
- Installation Invitations, 1973 (Box 15)
- Non-Sexist Christian Liturgy, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
- Freshman Mailing, 1973 (Box 15)
- Annual Conference, 1975 (Box 15)
- Founder's Day Service, 1973 (Box 15)
- United Methodist Campus Ministry, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
- Rabbi Robert Siegel, 1973-1977 (Box 15)
- O'Brien, Andrew J., 1975-1977 (Box 15)
- Vergel Lattimore, 1976 (Box 15)
- Phillips, Frances, 1976 (Box 15)
- Wilson Gunn, 1977 (Box 15)
- Chapel Staff, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
- Durham Ministers' Association, 1974 (Box 15)
- Robert Murrell, 1973-1976 (Box 15)
- DUCC Budget Committee Records -- Info on 1974-1975 Requests (Box 15)
- DUPM Staff, 1976-1977 (Box 15)
- Weyhausen, Vana, 1978 (Box 15)
- Ben Smith, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
- McConkey, David B., 1979-1980 (Box 15)
- Summer Preachers, 1978 (Box 15)
- Sylvester, Chaplain Bruce R., 1975-1979 (Box 15)
- Guest Preachers, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
- Summer Preaching Schedule, 1975-1979 (Box 15)
- Leslie, Rev. Dr. Reo N., 1979-1980 (Box 15)
- Thomas, Rev. James R., 1979-1980 (Box 16)
- Harriott Quinn, 1978-1980 (Box 16)
- Fiftieth Anniversary Replies, 1980 (Box 16)
- Preaching Invitations, 1975-1976 (Box 16)
- Preaching Invitations Accepted, undated (Box 16)
- Preaching Invitations Rejected, 1974-1977 (Box 16)
- NACUC/ACURA, 1975-1979 (Box 16)
- A Service of Thanksgiving for the Life of Tracy Edward Bridges, 1980 (Box 16)
- DUCC Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
- NACUC Resources, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
- NACUC Notes, 1979 (Box 16)
- Religious Life Staff, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
- DUPM Staff, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
- Chapel Staff, 1979-1982 (Box 16)
- Shearer, Elizabeth, 1980 RESTRICTED (Box 16)
- Annual Conference, 1981 (Box 16)
- Amahl and the Night Visitors, 1979 (Box 16)
- Baccalaureate Preacher Sub-Committee, 1979 (Box 16)
- Baccalaureate Service, 1981 (Box 16)
- Commencement Committee, 1981 (Box 16)
- Community Ecumenical Service, 1979 (Box 16)
- Concert Schedule, 1977-1978 (Box 16)
- Convocation and Pastors School, 1980 (Box 16)
- Children's Year Service, 1979 (Box 16)
- Crop Walk, 1979 (Box 16)
- Duke University Campus Ministry, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
- Hamilton Vespers, 1981 (Box 17)
- Weadon, David, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
- International Year of the Child, 1979 (Box 17)
- Messiah, 1978 (Box 17)
- Medical Center Alumni Weekend, 1976 (Box 17)
- Newton, Clint, 1979 (Box 17)
- Nursing School Administrative Staff, 1975-1976 (Box 17)
- Partin, Annette, undated (Box 17)
- St. Matthew Passion, 1981 (Box 17)
- United Fund Budget Committee, 1977-1980 (Box 17)
- Verdi Requiem, 1978 (Box 17)
- Youth Day, 1977 (Box 17)
- Western North Carolina Conference Appointments, 1978-1979 (Box 17)
- Chapel Attendant Position, 1973-1982 RESTRICTED (Box 17)
- Value Groups, 1975 (Box 17)
- Tanner, Douglas, 1981-1982 (Box 17)
- National Institute for Campus Ministries, 1975-1977 (Box 17)
- Personal Subscriptions, 1974 (Box 17)
- Political Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 17)
- Personal Correspondence Addresses, 1971 (Box 17)
- Student Affairs Staff, 1980-1982 (Box 17)
- Sparks, Donna, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
- Preaching Schedule, 1975-1976 (Box 17)
- Religious Life Staff, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
- Southeastern Jurisdictional Conference, 1980 (Box 17)
- North Carolina Council of Churches, 1976-1980 (Box 17)
- Investment Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 18)
- Miscellaneous, 1978-1982 (Box 18)
- Cleland Fund Acknowledgements in Memory of Mr. Muirhead, 1976-1977 (Box 18)
- Annual Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 18)
- Commencement Committee, 1979 (Box 18)
- Baccalaureate Preacher, 1978-1979 RESTRICTED (Box 18)
- Child Advocacy Commission of Durham, 1978-1979 (Box 18)
- Flood Relief Western North Carolina, 1977 (Box 18)
- Orientation, 1977 (Box 18)
- Regional Directors NACUC, 1975-1977 (Box 18)
- Chapel Staff, 1978-1979 (Box 18)
- Sampson, Brenda, 1979 RESTRICTED (Box 18)
- Major Jerome Honeycutt Memorial Service, 1979 (Box 18)
- Continuing Education for Campus Ministry Conference, 1977 (Box 18)
- Publications, 1973 (Box 18)
- United Methodist Campus Ministry, 1974 (Box 18)
- United Ministries in Higher Education, 1974 (Box 18)
- Western North Carolina Conference, 1975 (Box 18)
- Fowler, Alyce, 1978-1979 (Box 18)
- DUPM Staff, 1978-1979 (Box 18)
- DUPM Advisory Council, 1978-1979 (Box 18)
- Order of Worship -- Duke Chapel, 1973 (Box 18)
- Baptist Student Union Newsletter, 1979 (Box 18)
- Rev. Robert Young Budget Book, 1977 (Box 18)
- NACUC, 1974-1979 (Box 18)
- Former Duke Chapel Preachers (Box 19)
  - Bishop A. James Armstrong, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Myron S. Augsburger, 1971, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Browne Barr, 1966-1969 (Box 19)
  - Bishop Stephen F. Bayne, Jr., Anglican, 1961-1971 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Eugene Carson Blake -- President, National Council of Churches, Phil., PA, 1955-1957 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Jerald C. Brauer, Lutheran -- Dean, The Federated Theological Faculty, Chicago, IL, 1956-1961 (Box 19)
  - J. Russell Chandran, 1965-1972 (Box 19)
  - William S. Coffin, 1967-1989 (Box 19)
  - Evans E. Crawford, 1966-1978 (Box 19)
  - C. A. Coulson, Methodist, 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - G. Henton Davies, 1959-1969 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Nels Fredrik Solomon Ferre, Lutheran, 1954-1963 (Box 19)
  - Ferre-Tillich, 1990 (Box 19)
  - Valdo Galland, 1969-1970 (Box 19)
  - Dean Samuel Gandy, 1965-1969 (Box 19)
  - John Garrett, 1965-1967 (Box 19)
  - Bishop John E. Hines -- Presiding Bishop, Protestant Episcopal Church of the U.S., 1964-1970 (Box 19)
  - Dr. and Mrs. Douglas Horton, Congregationalist -- Dean, Harvard Div. School, 1955-1963 (Box 19)
  - John A. Hutchison, Presbyterian, 1959 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Philip A. Johnson, 1967-1969 (Box 19)
  - Dow Kirkpatrick, 1964-1969 (Box 19)
  - Jorge Lara-Braud, 1964-1971 (Box 19)
  - James M. Lawson, Jr., 1971 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Robert E. Luccock, Congregational, 1961-1962 (Box 19)
  - John D. Maguire, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Bishop Rajah Manikam, Lutheran, 1957-1966 (Box 19)
  - Principal John Marsh -- Mansfield College, Oxford, England, 1956-1965 (Box 19)
  - Jose Miguez Bonino, 1966-1972 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Albert Theodore Mollegen, Episcopalian, 1952-1962 (Box 19)
  - Jurgen D. Moltmann, 1967-1973 (Box 19)
  - Colin Morris, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Dean Walter G. Muelder, 1963 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Roy Nichols, 1967-1984 (Box 19)
  - Harold Ockenga, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Albert C. Outler, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Dean Edward H. Patey, Liverpool, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Chester A. Pennington, 1962-1977 (Box 19)
  - Rev. J. F. Peter, Presbyterian -- Australia, 1954-1959 (Box 19)
  - Harry M. Philpott, Southern Baptist, 1959-1970 (Box 19)
  - Joachim Pillai, Ceylong, 1972-1976 (Box 19)
  - Dr. W. Kenneth Pope, Methodist, 1959-1963 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Samuel Proctor, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Bishop Richard C. Raines, Methodist, 1959-1960 (Box 19)
  - Dr. David H. C. Read, Presbyterian, 1963-1975 (Box 19)
  - E. C. Pete Reckard, 1965-1970 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Elfan Rees, Geneva, Congregational, 1953-1963 (Box 19)
  - Milton Robinson, 1967 (Box 19)
  - Isabel Rogers, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Ruth Rohlfs, 1971 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Culbert Rutenger, Baptist, 1954-1969 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Eduard Schweizer, Zurich, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Robert Shinn, Evangelical and Reformed, 1954 (Box 19)
  - Joseph Sittler, Lutheran, 1954-1962 (Box 19)
  - Tom Skinner, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Eugene L. Smith, 1964 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Donald Soper, British Methodist, 1959-1975 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Douglas V. Steere, Quaker, 1956-1967 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Edmond A. Steimle, Lutheran, 1959-1972 (Box 19)
  - Bishop W. McFerrin Stowe, 1969 (Box 19)
  - Dr. D. Elton Trueblood, Friends, 1954-1972 (Box 19)
  - T. Paul Verghese, 1967-1970 (Box 19)
  - Rev. Alan Walker, Methodist, 1955-1968 (Box 19)
  - John Seldon Whale, Congregational, 1959-1968 (Box 19)
  - Samuel S. Wiley, 1969-1971 (Box 19)
  - Rev. Colin W. Williams, Methodist, 1954-1966 (Box 19)
- Former Duke Chapel Preachers (Box 20)
  - Brad Abernathy, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Theodore F. Adams, Baptist, 1953-1959 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Eddy Asirvatham, 1954-1968 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Edwin Aubrey, 1954 (Box 20)
  - Dr. John Baillie, 1956-1957 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Roland H. Bainton, Congregationalist, 1953-1970 (Box 20)